为了在第一时间做出中文字幕，
前面这段和前情提要暂且不做翻译
请谅解(换用新浪微博@核桃KD)
Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
Pan Am flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe
and the Middle East.
This will not stand, this
aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
This relentless
pursuit of terror.
We will make no distinction...
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
...until something stops him.
It was right
in front of my eyes,
and I never saw it coming.
That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
You're the smartest
and the dumbest fucking person
I've ever known.
I'm not the
one who got it wrong.
I'm the only one
who got it right.
Take 'em.
Take 'em all.
Homeland - 3x10
"Good Night"
Previously on Homeland...
The bomber's the only way
to prove that Brody's innocent.
What the fuck
are you doing, Carrie?
Carrie, turn around now.
This is your last warning.
We got a gunshot wound
to the upper left bicep.
Significant bleeding.
Might have clipped an artery.
Where the fuck is Saul?
He's not what we expected.
But he's what we've got.
The guy's a junkie... sir.
I'm offering you the chance
to be a Marine again.
No more. I...
I'm done.
I have a play.
It involves Brody.
- You told me Javadi was the play.
- He is.
Brody's the next phase.
So, what is it?
What's your big idea?
Darnish Akbari.
Head of Iran's
Revolutionary Guard.
Right.
Javadi's boss.
And the single greatest
impediment to peace.
I want him gone.
Brody can get to him.
Do what Saul's asking.
What you're asking.
All right, what I'm asking.
Look at me, Carrie.
You couldn't send me out for
a pack of cigarettes right now.
We'll get you ready.
You just have to be willing.
The guys get me to the border
where I surrender myself?
Correct, and we chose
Marivan, because
several Al Qaeda commanders
also asked
for political asylum there.
What make you think
I'll ever get close enough
to General Akbari
to take him out?
Javadi's on the ground.
We'll facilitate a meeting
between the two of you.
I will come back from Tehran.
I know you will.
And not just for her.
Brody?
See you on the other side.
Carrie
Carrie.
我们需要谈一谈
We need to talk.
谈什么？
What about?
关于你的肩膀？
How's your shoulder?
跟新的一样好
Brand fucking new.
我想消除咱们之间的误会
I want to clear the air
就是在汽车旅馆Franklin那一团糟之后
after that clusterfuck
with Franklin at the motel.
我没有兴趣
I'm not interested.
我已经厌倦那些鬼话
I'm so tired of
all the bullshit
和那些掩饰自己的人们，我甚至不想和你说话
and people covering their asses,
I can't even tell you.
那是一个直接的命令，Carrie
It was a direct order, Carrie.
我不想冒险让别人来开那枪
I didn't want to risk letting
someone else take the shot.
当你在做手术的时候，
While you were in surgery,
我看了一下你的医疗记录
I took a look
at your medical records.
你怎么？！
You what?!
我当时很担心我对你造成的伤害
I was worried
about the damage I'd done.
Carrie，你已经怀孕15个星期了
Carrie, you're
15 weeks pregnant.
- 所以呢？
- So?
- 所以，我认为
- So, I think
你应该考虑退出这次行动
you should consider sitting
this part of the operation out.
我为什么要那么做？
And why would I do that?
因为你不可能在这种情况下
Because it's impossible
for you to be objective
保持客观
under the circumstances.
这种情况是，我怀了Brody的孩子吗？
The circumstances being,
I'm carrying Brody's child?
是的
Yes.
好的，首先，孩子不是他的
Well, first of all,
it's not his,
非常谢谢你。其次呢，
thank you very much.
Second of all,
这跟你没有关系
it's none of your
damn business,
跟其他人也没有关系
or anyone else's,
所以你离我远点
so just stay the fuck
out of my way.
_
半生半熟的？
Medium rare?
嗯
Hmm.
很好吃，是吧？
Pretty fucking tasty, huh?
嗯...嗯，是的
Hmm... hmm. Yeah.
诀窍就是在隔断他的喉咙之前
The secret is to relax the goat
先让山羊放松
before you cut his throat.
这就是为什么Modarres牙关紧闭而且膝盖疼痛
Which is why Modarres
has lockjaw and sore knees.
- 他们怎么样？
- How are they doing?
- 嗯
- Mm.
不错。穿过Kurdistan的行动平静无事
Good. That move across
Kurdistan was uneventful.
现在...
Now...
他们就在那边。他们正在等待夜幕降临，那个时候
that's them right there. They're waiting
for nightfall, at which point,
他们讲开车送他(Brody)到边境上
they'll drive him
right up to the border
这里，将掩护他通过伊朗的人工检查点
here, cover him across
to the manned checkpoint
就在那边
on the Iranian side,
right there.
国际事件的风险
The risk
of an international incident
是总统非常关心的一个问题
is a serious concern
for the President.
我们非常确信那些我们告诉他的东西
We stand 100%
behind what we told him.
行动的回报值得我们冒这个险
The risk of this operation
is worth the reward.
而且，不太可能有什么事出错
And in the unlikely event
anything goes wrong,
我们都搞定了
we have it covered.
我都不想问这到底意味着什么
I'm not even going to
ask what that means.
他今晚所要做的就是
All he has to do tonight
穿过边境，请求政治避难
is walk across the border
and ask for asylum.
就是这样
That's it.
海军陆战队都这么做吗？
Is that a Marine thing?
将袜子里外翻个个儿，穿新的一面
Turn the socks inside out,
get the fresh side.
没有一面是新的
Well, there is no fresh side.
一面全是汗，另一面脏了
One side's sweaty,
and the other's just dirty.
好吧，也许我脑子里知道的就是这些
Well, maybe it's just
all in my head.
有用吗？
Does it work?
看着我
Well, look at me.
我是一个新人
I'm a new man.
通信检查
Comms check.
Kilo-Alpha，我是Zero
Kilo-Alpha, this is Zero.
我们看见了
We have visual.
发送信号强度，完毕
Send signal strength. Over.
Kilo-Alpha
Kilo-Alpha.
信号强度10
Signal strength ten.
Kilo-Bravo，我是Zero，完毕
Kilo-Bravo,
this is Zero. Over.
Bravo.强度也是10
Bravo. Also strength ten.
Zero,我是Kilo-Alpha
Zero, this is Kilo-Alpha.
视野良好
New Moon, visibility good.
又是天堂的一天
Another day in paradise.
乘客(这里指Brody)怎么样？
How's the passenger doing?
不是很糟
Not bad.
对于一个锅盖头(美国海军陆战队士兵的谐称)来说
For a fucking jarhead.
就是这样了。Alpha完毕
That is all. Alpha out.
Bravo完毕
Bravo out.
越过边境后他要走到哪里？
What's he walking into
at the border crossing point?
嗨，Gene，你能把边界图片调出来吗？
Hey, Gene, can you bring up
the border photos, please?
马上出来
Coming up.
两个小时前
Yeah, as of two hours ago,
一个兵舍，里面有8个人，又一个中士指挥
one barrack hut for eight men,
commanded by a sergeant.
路边的守卫每四个小时换一次
Roadside guard hut manned
in four-hour shifts
他们有两个装备自动武器的人
by two men with
automatic weapons.
有没有关于伊朗巡逻队
Any updates on the Iranian
无线电通信的最新消息？
border patrol radio traffic?
每小时进行一次通信检查
Hourly comms checks.
一个请求需要更多的粮食
Plus, one request
for more ration packs,
还有两个关于无线电电池的请求
two for new radio batteries.
8个无聊的又饥饿的应征士兵
Eight bored
and hungry conscripts
他们的无线电已经被我们接入
whose radios we're dialed into.
没有低估他们的可能性吧？
No chance of
underestimating them then?
没有
Fair point.
我们再来回顾一遍你用来掩护的故事
Let's go over your cover story
最后一次
one last time.
爆炸之后，
After the bombing,
Nazir的网络中有人在Langley附近留了车
Nazir's network left a car
near Langley,
我开车进入森林，到达了加拿大边境
which I took into the woods
on the Canadian border,
在那里，我把头剃了，继续步行
where I shaved my head,
and I continued on foot.
然后我偷了一只船穿过芬迪湾，
There I stole a boat
across the Bay Of Fundy
到达新斯科舍，在那里，我遇见了一个
to Nova Scotia,
where I met a guy
与Amer El-Maati有关系的人
who had ties with Amer El-Maati,
他把我装进集装箱中送往哥伦比亚
who put me in a shipping
container to Colombia.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
然后，为(黎巴嫩)真主党工作的雇佣兵
Then, mercenaries
working with Hezbollah
将我带到了委内瑞拉，在那里，我最后被放进
took me across to Venezuela,
where they finally put me
一架国家石油公司的飞机上，
into a state oil company plane
飞到了伊朗
to a strip in Iraq,
我被交给了基地组织，
where I was handed over
to an Al Qaeda cell
然后他们带我穿过边境来到了伊朗
who were tasked with getting me
across the border to Iran.
加入基地组织，看看这个世界
Join Al Qaeda, see the world.
最后一个检查，夜晚的视野
Final checks. Night vision.
夜晚视野传送进来了
Night vision transmissions
coming online.
我的口香糖吃完了
I'm out of Black Jack.
你那里还有吗？
Any more out there?
一切都还好吧，sir？
Everything okay, sir?
最后一个了？
This the last pack?
我还有很多呢
I got you plenty more.
别担心
Don't worry.
你写过信吗？
Did you write a letter?
什么？
What?
写给家里
Home.
说声再见
To say good-bye.
如果我做过，你们肯定都知道
Pretty sure you guys
would know if I did.
你可以把这事安排给你的CIA朋友
You could've arranged it
就是那个金发碧眼的
with your, uh, CIA friend,
the blonde.
你怎么样？
How you doing?
很好，你呢？
Good. You?
好像我正在维加斯用(房屋)抵押赌博
Feel like I'm in Vegas
betting the mortgage.
大家准备好了
Stand by, people.
好戏考试了
Show time.
Reaper1出什么事了？
What's going on with Reaper 1?
传感器带宽问题
Sensor bandwidth issues.
时常发生。我们正在重新设置
It happens.
We're resetting.
不过几分钟，一切都会好的
All being well, shouldn't
be more than a couple minutes.
一切都会好的？
"All being well"?
我们要压住队伍停滞不前，
Are we holding the team back
直到无人机重新恢复吗？
until the drone's back on line?
那个无人机主要是为我们工作
That drone's mainly for us.
他们有卫星电话和夜视
They have satphones
and night vision.
没有它(无人机)，他们现在能够向边境靠近的
They can move closer to the
border without it for now.
- *
- 什么？
- Shit.
- What?
去边境的路基本上是堵了
Road to the border's
as good as blocked.
外地的汽油卡车正在用免费的汽油贿赂当地官员
Foreign gas trucks paying off
local officials with free gas.
警察，军队，不管你怎么叫他们，全都在受贿
Cops, military, you name it,
all on the take.
边境在哪里？
Where's the border?
就在同一条路上，过了他们的1英里处
Another mile past 'em
on this same road.
那些远处的灯光
Those lights in the distance.
Zero,Kilo-Alpha，完毕
Zero, Kilo-Alpha, over.
Zero发送完毕
Zero send, over.
你看到我正在看的东西了吗？
See what I'm seeing?
是的，等他们结束
Yeah. Wait out.
伙计们，出来
Guys, get out.
搞得让那些路过的人看起来像是车坏了
Make it look like car trouble
for anybody passing.
我们是有一个备用计划吧？
We have a backup plan, right?
是的，我们正在等Langley确认替代路线
Yeah. We're waiting for Langley
to confirm the alternate route.
我需要雄蜂(无人驾驶机)。好了还是没有？
Now, I need that drone.
Are we gonna have it or not?
收到
Copy that.
怎么这么长时间？
What's taking them so long?
我不知道。他们遇到了无人机技术故障
I don't know. They had
a technical with the drone.
我们要在这里坐多久
So how long are we gonna
sit here for?
你比我的孩子们还遭
Shit, man,
you're worse than my kids.
那些后方指挥所的混账东西
God, those rear echelon
motherfuckers.
无人机出问题了
Got a problem with the drone.
真是个好的开始
That's a good start.
Reaper恢复正常
Reaper's back.
好的
Good.
现在我们来看一下
Now let's get eyes
进入边境的替代路线
on that alternate
route into the border.
正在重新定位
Repositioning now.
Kilo-Alpha，Zero
Kilo-Alpha, Zero.
无人机恢复正常，正在探测路线
Drone is back online.
Scouting your route.
等着
Wait out.
又嚼起你的幸运口香糖了？
Back to chewing
your lucky gum again?
是的，你也来一个？
Yeah. You want a stick?
*
Shit.
头低下
Put your head down.
假装睡觉，别动
Like you're sleeping.
Don't move.
Zero,Kilo-Bravo。准备好了
Zero, Kilo-Bravo. Stand by.
Alpha的车好像出了点问题
May have a situation
with the Alpha vehicle.
当地警察出现了
Local cops just rolled up.
马格利布（北非的一地区）
Maghreb.
你们问什么在这里？
Why are you here?
正要去Marivan
Going to Marivan.
基地组织
...Al Qaeda.
他们对掩护的故事不买账
They're not
buying the cover story.
天哪，他们想看一下卡车
Jesus, they want to look
in the truck.
说那句话，Kilo-Alpha
Say the word,
Kilo-Alpha.
- 什么话？
- What word?
- “晚安”
- "Good night."
他们应该在警察看到Brody之前说声“晚安”
They should say "Good night"
before the cops see Brody.
(穆斯林问候)
As-salamu alaykum.
晚...安
Good... night.
嗨...
Hey...
你还好吧？
You okay?
Brody?你还好吗？
Brody? You good?
嗨
Hey.
- 你干什么？
- What the fuck are you doing?
- 我做不了这个
- I can't do it.
- 可以，你可以的
- Yes, you can.
- 我不行，不行
- I can't. No.
- 我不行，不，我不行
- I can't. No, I fucking can't.
- 你会的
- And you will.
我不行。我...
I fucking can't. I fucking...
现在说这些晚了(直译实在太过直接，还是大家意会一下)
Bit late in the day
for your vagina to chime in.
滚
Fuck off...
你害怕了？
You scared?
你是不是害怕了？
Are you fucking scared?
嗯
Mm-hmm. Mmm. I'm...
- 我怕了。我怕了
- I'm scared. I'm scared.
- 好的
- Good.
我也是。我看到过太多的人
Me, too. I've seen
way too many men
在这个肮脏的第三世界被杀害
killed out here in this
third world toilet.
就我个人而言，每次他们派我回到这里我都很不爽
I personally shit myself every
time they send me back here.
如果你现在不走(指继续任务)
And if you don't snap out
of this right now
我们今晚都可能死在这里
we could all fucking die
here tonight.
这就是你想要的？
Is that what you want?
不
No.
告诉我你准备好了
Tell me you're gonna be okay.
告诉我这不是你的末路
Tell me that this is not
the end of the road for you.
- 不不不...
- No, no, no...
- 我需要听见你说
- I need to hear you say it.
我会...
I'll be...
我会好的.我准备好了
I will be okay. I'm okay.
我没事了
I'm okay.
I'll be okay.
Kilo-Alpha，发生什么事了吗？
Kilo-Alpha, is there a problem?
Brody晕车了，他吐了
Passenger got carsick.
He threw up
现在我们准备好了
and we're ready to roll.
晕车？
Carsick?
这是安全卫星链路。你能告诉他们
It's a secure sat link.
Can you tell them to just
- 停止废话么？
- cut the bullshit?
- 他没事吧？
- Is he gonna be okay?
他没事的
Fuckin'-A he's gonna be okay.
给
Here.
擦掉你脸上的血
Wipe the blood off your face.
Kilo-Alpha
Kilo-Alpha,
kilo-Bravo，继续前进至替代路线的交叉点
Kilo-Bravo, proceed
to alternate crossing point.
知道了
Roger.
Alpha完毕
Alpha out.
我们刚才是不是杀了三个伊朗的警察官？
Did we or did we not just kill
three Iraqi police officers?
不要再小事上斤斤计较
Kurdish-- not to split hairs.
不管怎样，这并不是总统需要知道的
Either way, this isn't something
the President needs to know.
哦，我懂了，相信我
Oh, I understand.
Believe me.
帮我接JSOC(联合特种作战司令部)司令官
Get me JSOC Commander now.
这整个地区基本上就是无人区
This whole area is
pretty much a no-man's land
从伊朗伊拉克战争之后
since the Iran-Iraq war.
有人来了
We got visitors.
- 议员，将军
- Senator. General.
- 指挥官
- Director.
- 白宫...
- The White House...
- 我知道
- I know.
- 我被告知你会来
- I was told you were coming.
- 让我讲完
- Let me finish.
白宫派Pfister将军和我
The White House sent
General Pfister and me
过来观察和指导
to advise and observe.
指导，观察
Advise and observe.
JSOC司令官来指导；我自己...
The JSOC Commander, to advise;
myself, the President's nomin...
Higgins告诉了你们关于行动的哪些事情？
What did Higgins tell you
about the operation?
这次行动打算迅速，悄无声息，不留血迹的结束
That this part was meant to be
quick and silent and bloodless.
他告诉了你一切，不是吗？
He told you everything,
didn't he?
是的，他说了一切
Yes, he did.
- 包括...？
- Including...?
- 中士Brody，是的
- Sergeant Brody, yes.
Saul...
不管怎样，
whatever this turns out to be,
是天才之举还是其它什么
bold stroke of genius
or otherwise,
我注定要继承这一切
I'm destined to inherit it.
所以既然已经在行动中了
So now that it's actually
in motion,
不管好坏
for better or for worse,
我没有选择，只能希望它能成功了
I have no choice
but to wish it every success.
单独说几句可以吗，议员？
A word in private, Senator?
不好意思，Bill
Excuse us, Bill.
当然
Of course.
你答应给我的喘息空间呢？
What about the breathing room
you agreed to give me?
交易时我推迟上任听证会
The deal was that I delay
my confirmation hearing,
这个我已经做到了
which I've done.
那个义务已经被履行了
That obligation
has been fulfilled.
祝你好运吧，Saul
Consider yourself lucky, Saul,
是Higgins打给我们电话，而不是总统
that Higgins called us
and not the President
或者他的国家安全顾问
or his National
Security Advisor.
明白了
Copy that.
明白
Copy.
- Mathison小姐
- Ms. Mathison.
- 议员
- Senator.
你的肩膀怎么样？
How's your shoulder?
医生告诉我你非常幸运
Doctor told me you
were very lucky.
我很好，谢谢你的关心
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
我能说的就是你肯定是一个极好的营销员
All I can say is you must be
one hell of a salesperson
才能让Brody做这件事情
to get Brody to do this.
在局里，我们都叫这个是招募
Here at the Agency,
we call that recruiting.
这里，看一下
Here. Take a look.
距离边境还有一半的路
Border's a click
and a half away.
过了那个房子300码
300 yards past that building.
只不过是一个浅溪，12码宽
All it is is a shallow stream,
12 yards across.
听着...我马上开车带你过去
Listen... I'm gonna
drive you right up to it
然后我们都会看着你
and we're all gonna
be watching you.
你穿过那条河，然后径直走向另一边的林木线
You way across that river and you head
up to that treeline on the other side.
你一到那里，朝北往回走3英里
Once you hit it, follow
it north for three miles
到达伊朗检查点
back to the Iranian checkpoint
就是我们起初要把你放下的位置
where we were
originally gonna drop you.
嗨，你去哪？
Hey, where you going?
撒尿
Piss.
跟他一起去
Go with him.
我们发现两个可能的敌人
We got potential bogeys.
两个伊朗军队的的悍马
Two Iraqi army hummers
三次出现在我们信号的南边
three clicks south
of our call sign.
Kilo-Alpha，南边出现两辆伊朗的悍马
Kilo-Alpha, we have
two Iraqi hummers
不是什么太重要的事情，但是注意了
three clicks south, it's not a
significant threat but be aware.
Alpha知道了
Alpha Roger.
好的，我们得知伊朗巡逻队3次出现在南边
All right, we got an Iraqi
patrol three clicks south.
不是什么大事，但是地势困难
It's not that big a deal but
it's difficult terrain out there
所以我们得行动迅速，安静
so we got to move quick, quiet
而且动静小，也就是说只有我和他出去
and small now, which means
it's just me and him from here.
你们剩下的人待在这儿，利用这里做掩护
Rest of you guys stay here,
cover from this position.
有问题吗？
Questions?
准备好了吗？
Ready?
是的
Yeah.
当你还是一个小孩的时候，你当时想长大后当什么？
When you were a little kid,
what did you want to be when you grew up?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
胡说
Bullshit.
每个人都会记得的
Everyone remembers.
你不用在管我了
You don't
have to manage me anymore, man.
我知道我来这里是做什么的
I know what I'm here to do.
只是和你聊聊
Just making conversation's all.
那是什么？
What's that?
不是什么？
Nothing.
那你想当什么呢？
Well, what did you want to be?
我在得克萨斯长大
I grew up in Texas.
我想做的就是骑牛
All I wanted to do
was ride bulls.
那你为什么没有？
Yeah, why didn't you?
我骑了
I did.
2年
Two years.
但是我的粉丝受不了打击
But my nuts couldn't
take the beating.
所以现在我做这个
So now I do this.
真欢乐...
Happy fucking...
刚才发生了什么？
What just happened?
Kilo-Alpha,我是Zero，请回话
Kilo-Alpha,
this is Zero, over.
Kilo-Alpha,我是Zero，请回话
Kilo-Alpha, this is Zero, over.
Kilo-Alpha, Zero, over.
Zero,我是Kilo-Bravo
Zero, this is Kilo-Bravo.
Alpha碰到了什么
Alpha hit something.
一个地雷或者是简易爆炸装置
A mine or an IED.
屏幕上能看见敌人吗？
Any hostiles on your screens?
准备检查
Stand by. Checking now.
目前而言，没有什么
Nothing, so far.
Sir，那个伊拉克巡逻队
Sir, that Iraqi patrol
刚刚转向北边，朝着爆炸的地点过来
just turned north,
towards the explosion.
现在我们必须告诉总统
Now we have to call
the President.
等一下。让尘土先落下来
Wait.
Let the dust settle first.
不，任何造成国际事件的可能性
No, any possibility of
an international incident
- 我都必须告诉总统？
- I must call the President.
- 你必须做得是
- What you must do
保持冷静的头脑
is keep a cool head
而且不要慌张
and take great care
not to panic.
好吧，我至少得通知伊拉克人
Well, we at least have
to call the Iraqis.
说什么？
And say what?
让你的巡逻队掉头，我们有一个CIA队伍
Turn your patrol around,
we have a CIA team
之前没有告诉你们，在那片地方执行任务？
we didn't tell you about,
operating in the area?
那个无人机是有武器装备的，对吧？
That drone is armed, correct?
Zero，我是Kilo-Bravo
Zero, Kilo-Bravo.
我们马上到Kilo-Alpha
We're one click out
from Kilo-Alpha.
知道了，kilo-Bravo，多加小心
Roger, Kilo-Bravo, be advised
伊拉克巡逻队正则逼近你们的位置
that Iraqi patrol is closing
on your position.
Sir，白宫打电话过来了
Sir, White House
is on the line.
放到屏幕上
Put him on the screen.
Mike
Mike.
- 我可能有一个解决方案
- I may have a solution.
- 请说
- Please.
那个无人机装备有4颗导弹
That drone has four
Hellfire missiles on it.
你是说我们与伊拉克巡逻队交战？
You saying we engage
the Iraqi patrol?
我是说我们刚才发现了基地组织
I'm saying we just found
an Al Qaeda cell
正在视图偷运美国头号恐怖分子到伊朗
trying to smuggle America's most
wanted terrorist into Iran
我们用无人机干掉了他们
and we take them out
with that drone.
天哪
Jesus.
如果他们死了，这就是一个很聪明的局
It's a smart play
if they're dead.
- 那如果他们没死呢？他根本不在乎他们是死是活
- And if they're not dead? - He doesn't
care whether they're dead or alive,
他所在乎的就是收拾自己的烂摊子
all he fucking gives a shit
about is covering his own ass.
- 闭上你的嘴，Carrie，嘴闭严
- Bite your lip, Carrie. Bite it hard.
- *
- Fuck.
那个伊朗可巡逻队赶过来还得分钟？
That Iraqi patrol is,
what, a minute away?
让我说的清楚点，Mike
Let me be very clear, Mike.
我绝不会下令对我们自己人的攻击
I will not order
a strike on our own men.
挂断
Hang it up.
我们发现Alpha汽车里面有动静
We've got movement
in the Alpha vehicle.
要不就是汽车刚刚静下来
Either the vehicle just settled
要不就是我发现第二个热信号在移动
or I have a second
heat signature moving.
第二个人在移动
The second figure is moving.
他们活着，他们都活着
They're alive;
they're both alive.
我的腿
My leg.
***
Motherfucker...
不
No.
- 我的腿...
- My fucking leg...
- 好的，坐起来
- All right, sit up.
坐起来，坐起来
Sit up, sit up.
双臂合十
Fold your arms.
好的，跟我来
Okay, come with me.
好的...
All right...
电话，卫星电话...
Phone, satphone.
- Kilo-Bravo,我是Alpha，请回答
- Kilo-Bravo, this is Alpha, over.
- 我是Bravo，说
- Bravo, send.
我们在边境西边的一个房子中
We're in the building
to the west of the border,
没有敌人的火力，受伤人员任然有意识
no enemy fire;
casualty is still conscious
他是他失去了一条腿，并且大量流血
but he's lost a leg
and a lot of blood, over.
Bravo，知道了，60秒后到达你的位置
Bravo, Roger.
Your location 60 seconds, over.
发现一个持枪小队在高地上
Get a gun team
up on high ground.
我暂时可以解决休克问题，阻止流血
I can treat for shock
and stem the blood flow for now.
别着急，按照我们的路线进来
Take your time to follow
our exact route in, over.
明白了
On it. Out.
想你的孩子们
Focus on your kids.
笨蛋，我没有孩子
I don't have any kids, dumbass.
随便谈一谈，因为你当时就是个小孩子
Making small talk 'cause
you were being a fucking baby.
我们一定会把你带出去
We're gonna get you out of here.
抽烟
Smoke.
给我一些烟
Here, give me some
of my cigarettes.
我从来没想过我会是现在这个家伙
I never thought I'd
be this fucking guy.
我也没有
No, me neither.
我猜是我完蛋了
I guess I fucked up, T.
Beers on you, then.
我给他打了一针吗啡
I gave him one morphine shot.
他就剩一个了
He's got one left.
我们得马上走
We got to haul ass now.
抓住那个
Grab that.
这这这...
Here. Here... here.
翻过去
Roll... back.
好的
Okay.
- 准备好了吗？
- Ready to do this, boss?
- 是的
- Yeah.
好的，大家都回到卡车上去
All right, everybody
back to the truck.
- 走！
- Go!
- 我们走，快
- Let's go, quick.
伊拉斯巡逻队来了
Iraqi patrol
just joined the party.
Zero,我是Kilo-Bravo，联系！从南边发起了机械攻击
Zero, Kilo-Bravo, contact!
Automatic fire from the south.
一个排或者是一个连的火力
Platoon or possible
company strength.
尽全力不要将这个扩大化
Do all you can
not to escalate this.
压制回击火力，只能压制火力
Suppressive return fire.
Suppressive fire only.
别让他们在地面上，让他们转过去
Don't put them in the ground.
Just turn them around.
Zero，我是Kilo-Bravo，我们
Zero, Kilo-Bravo,
we don't get Aziz out
- 在几分钟内不能把Aziz带出来了，他死了
- in the next few minutes, he's dead.
- 伊拉克的信号正在
- Iraqi call signs
请求炮兵火力攻击
are requesting an artillery fire
mission up the chain.
我们的直升机有多远？
How far out are
our helicopters?
8分钟
Eight minutes.
将军，有什么建议？
General, advice?
我们没有8分钟了
Eight minutes
is time we don't have.
- 要不然我们打电话给伊拉克，和和他们说实话
- Either we call the Iraqis and level with
them...
- 我们也没有这个时间
- Also time we don't have
我们负担不起任何一次反攻
and every shade of blowback
we can't afford.
所以这就是要撤退到一个安全的登录区
So it's a fighting withdrawal
to a secure LZ,
就是后退远离他们刚才离开的那辆车
back five clicks in the vehicle
that they have left.
换句话说，我们得放弃任务
In other words,
we have to abort.
情报行动结束了
The intelligence
operation is over.
现在是军事行动，全靠你了，将军
It's a military one now.
It's all yours, General.
谢谢你
Thank you, sir.
向那些人开枪吧
Shoot the boys out of there.
知道了
Copy that. Comms.
Kilo-Bravo,我只Zero-Alpha
Kilo Bravo, this is Zero-Alpha.
Bravo，请说
Bravo, send.
- 我们将要用导弹来把他们打回去
- We're going to push them back
with Hellfire, over.
- 明白了
- Roger.
由你下令，在导弹的掩护下撤退
Withdraw with Hellfire
in support on your command.
我来下令，好的，等一下
On my command, roger, wait.
他们要放弃任务吗？
Are they aborting the mission?
Saul
Saul.
你运气不太好
You had some bad luck.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗨
Hey.
至少我们还有Javadi
At least we have Javadi.
他还在咱们的局中，不是什么都没有
He's still in play.
That's not nothing.
是的
Yeah.
准备导弹任务
Stand by for Hellfire
mission, over.
你们准备好了吗？
You guys ready?
后退！后退！
Fall back! Fall back!
- 我不会回去的
- I'm not gonna go back.
- 你***在说什么？
- What the fuck are you talking about? Yeah, you are.
我要闯过边境到伊朗，你是不能阻止我的
I'm gonna walk across that border into
Iran and you're not gonna to stop...
听我说，我现在在命令你后退
Listen to me! I am fucking ordering
you to fucking move out!
Brody拒绝撤退
Passenger refuses to withdraw,
我没有时间了，请指示
and I'm out of time.
Please advise.
不要留下任何人
Do not leave anyone behind.
我们在密集的火力下
We are under heavy fire!
伤员是第一位
The casualty is priority one,
Brody**不听话！
and the passenger is
non-fucking-compliant!
将军，请指示！
General, please advise!
让我跟他说
Let me talk to him.
如果有人能说服Brody撤退的话，一定是她
If anyone can talk Brody
down off a ledge, she can.
好的
All right.
让Brody接电话
Put the passenger on the line.
我再说一遍，让Brody接电话
I say again,
put the passenger on the line.
拿着
Take this.
Take it!
Brody？
Brody?
Brody，你能听见我吗？
Brody, can you hear me?
- 嗨，Brody！
- Hey, Brody!
- 他们正在放弃计划，Carrie！
- They're trying
to abort the mission, Carrie!
- 我知道
- I know.
- 好的，告诉他们***
- Well, tell them to go fuck themselves.
不，听我说
No, listen to me.
你自己一个人完成不了
You can't do this by yourself.
我距离边境就只剩300码了，Carrie
I'm 300 yards
from the border, Carrie.
我能做到的
I can make it.
你现在进入伊朗边境，你将完全只能看你自己了
You cross into Iran now and you will
be completely on your own.
说实话，我觉得这里也没有什么选择了
Well, to be honest I don't see
much of an option here.
选择就是撤退，再重新组织
The option is
to fall back, regroup,
我们之后会再找机会的
and we'll take another shot
at this later.
得了吧,Carrie，你知道这不会发生的
Come on, Carrie, you know
that's not gonna happen.
你不知道！
You don't know that!
停下来想一想
Now, stop and think
this through.
你没有地面支援
You have no sanction,
no support on the ground,
没有撤退计划
and no extraction plan.
你会死在那边的
You will die over there!
不，你错了，Carrie
No, you're wrong, Carrie.
你想知道为什么吗？
And you want to know why?
因为你能把我弄回去的
'Cause you're gonna get me home.
别这样说！别跟我说这个！
No, don't say that!
Do not put that on me.
这是个幻想
It's a fantasy.
你会有办法的
You'll find a way.
我有信心
I have faith.
就这样
That's all. Out.
不！Brody！Brody！
No, Brody! Brody!
*！
Fuck!
我们现在要撤退了
We are fucking moving out now.
所有人，走！
All of us. Let's go.
我不走
Not me.
他走了！***！
He's gone! Fuck him!
导弹袭击，快！
Hellfire, now! Hellfire, now!
Hellfire firing now.
走，走！
Move. Move now!
抓住他！
Grab him!
- 拿着
- Take it.
- 你要干什么？
- What are you doing?
把他带到着陆区，然后再来接我，走！
Get him to the LZ,
then come get me. Go!
*！
Fuck!
**的狙击手
Fucking snipers.
永远都固执的***
Always the stubborn
fucking assholes.
我能为你争取30秒时间来穿过边境
I can buy you 30 seconds
to cross that border
到达树林
and get to those trees.
我一旦开枪，你就跑
Once I start firing,
you start running.
如果你停了，我就亲手射杀你
And if you stop,
I'll fucking shoot you myself.
有问题吗？
Any questions?
- 没有
- No.
- 很好
- Oh, good.
数到三
Count of three.
1...2...3!
One... two... three!
那是什么？
What is that?
他们被包围了
They're surrounded.
被谁包围了？
Who by?
我们是不是遗漏了无线信号中的东西？
Are we picking up
anything on radios?
...Nicholas Brody
...Nicholas Brody.
_
伊朗人说他们有两个囚犯
The Iranians are saying
they have two prisoners.
确定是伊朗人而不是伊拉克人？
Are we sure it's the Iranians
and not the Iraqis?
100%确定
100%.
上帝
Jesus.
他们把伤员安全转移出
They got the
casualty out safely.
他现在很稳定
He's stable, on a bird
out to the carrier group now.
还有一些事情
There's something else.
什么？
What?
Brody成功越过边境
Brody made it across.
怎么做到的？
How?
他最后又跑了一次
He made a last second
run for it--
直接跑到了伊朗军事单位
headfirst
into an Iranian military unit.
他还好吧？
He's okay?
是的
Yes.
他成功了
He made it.
还有你，Saul
And you, Saul,
仍然在这场游戏中
are still in the game.
我糟透了
I'll be damned.
现在，这些家伙...
Right now, these guys...
他们被训练得对待任何越境的人
uh, they're trained
to treat anybody coming
都认为是以色列的特工
over the border
as Israeli agents.
你被折磨过...
You were tortured...
所以，告诉我接下来会发生什么
so tell me what to expect.
被击垮
Expect to break.
你当时维持了多长时间？
How long did you hold out?
我不知道
I don't know.
我当时根本没有时间概念
I lost track of time
pretty much right away,
但是，我想...
but I figure...
7天吧？
seven days?
足够让那些人
Enough time to allow the guys
改变他们的频率和作战计划了
to change their frequencies
and battle plans.
我只是...
I just...
我只是希望我能给你7天时间
I just hope
I can give you seven days
在德黑兰把事情搞定
to get the job done in Tehran.
嗯？
Huh?
嗨
Hi.
我能...？
May I?
当然可以
Of course.
Fara，你是这栋大楼里极少
Fara, you're one of the few
people in this building
知道Majid Javadi是局里的线人的人
who knows that Majid Javadi's
an Agency asset.
我不会告诉任何人的
I didn't breathe
a word to anybody.
我知道你不会，但这不是我来这里的原因
I know you didn't--
that's not why I'm here.
但是你在招募Javadi过程中扮演了非常重要的角色
But you had a crucial role
in recruiting Javadi.
事实上，Saul说过，没有你，这事就不可能成功
In fact, Saul says, without you,
it never would've come off.
他夸张了
He's exaggerating.
不过谢谢你
But thank you.
事情是这样的...
The thing is...
Javadi只是这个局的一半
Javadi's only half the play.
行动还有一个阶段
There's another phase
of the operation
你之前不知道的
you weren't made aware of.
这牵扯到一个线人，他的生命
It involves an asset,
whose life depends
取决于我们是否能在关键的时刻把他从伊朗解救出来
on us getting him out of Iran
at the critical moment.
事实是我们的营救计划
And the fact is
our extraction plan
刚才灰飞烟灭了
just went up in smoke.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Fara，你在得黑兰有一个叔叔
Fara, you have
an uncle in Tehran.
你爸爸的兄弟
Your father's brother.
- Carrie，不
- Carrie, no.
- 听我说完
- Just hear me out.
不，这太危险了
No, it's too dangerous.
- 我们所需要的就是...
- All we're asking for...
- 你在要求我
- You're asking me
将我的家人置于非常危险的境地
to put my family
at extreme risk.
你知道你是这样的
You know you are.
你忘了我直接目睹了
You forget I've seen firsthand
一场行动是多么快的失败了
how fast an operation
can go sideways.
告诉你事实
Tell the truth.
你永远不会要求你的家人这么做的
You would never ask your
own family to do this.
我也许会
I might.
从我对你叔叔的了解来看，他不是
And from what I know about
your uncle, he's not one
一个在大街上穿梭来避免麻烦的人
to cross the street to stay
out of trouble's way.
他是温和反对派的成员
He's a member of a moderate
opposition group.
不是扔炸弹的人
Not a bomb thrower.
我们所需要的就是城市里的一个地方来碰头
All we need is a place
to meet in the city.
一个实际上的安全屋
A de facto safe house.
Fara，我们有一个特工兄弟就在前线
Fara, we have a brother agent
in the field,
即将面临致命的危险
soon to be in mortal danger.
难道我们要欠他一个生还的机会吗？
Don't we owe him every chance
to get out alive?
嗨
Hey.
有人来了，有人来了
Someone's coming.
我的名字是Nicholas Brody...
My name is Nicholas Brody...
我正式向伊朗伊斯兰共和国
and I'm formally seeking asylum
寻求政治避难
in the islamic Republic of Iran.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
Ayman Jassim.
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
准备好什么？
Ready for what?
跟我去得黑兰
To go with me to Tehran.
那他呢
What about him?
不！***！
No! You fuck!
- 小声点，小声点！
- Quiet. Quiet!
- ***！
- You fucking asshole!
- 你这样做为什么？
- What did you do that for?!
- 控制一下你自己
- Control yourself.
- *！*！
- Fuck! Fuck!
- 平静一下！
- Calm down!
平静
Calm down.
现在
Now.
我们去得黑兰
We go to Tehran.
欢迎新浪微博@核桃KD，我们一起来做字幕